dogreatgood.com 2010-11-01

# DoGreatGood.com | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

InfoSpace, Inc. and its subsidiaries ("we", "us" or "our") owns and operates a number of different sites on the Web (each, an "InfoSpace Site"), including www.dogreatgood.com ("Do Great Good"), and is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our user community. This privacy policy provides details on our information collection and use practices that are specific to Do Great Good. For our general information collection, use and disclosure practices, please review our global privacy policy located here on the InfoSpace corporate website. Please note that this policy applies only to us and the Do Great Good website, and not to other companies or organizations or their web sites to which we may provide links or to any software that may be downloaded from the InfoSpace Sites.

## Anonymous User Information

We collect anonymous information each time you visit Do Great Good, and use this information to provide our services and improve the overall quality of your online experience. Each time you use our search services to submit a query, we collect your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type. We do not require you to share information that identifies you personally, such as your name or e-mail address, in order to use the search services available on Do Great Good. We collect this information by assigning an anonymous ID number to your queries and linking the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited Do Great Good, your search terms, and the links upon which you choose to click. Like most standard website servers, we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information.

## Individual User Information

From time-to-time we may collect or request information from you that identifies you personally in addition to the anonymous information described above. This information may include your contact information (such as name, e-mail address, shipping address, and zip code) and demographic information (such as age, gender, occupation, and household income). We will not use or disclose any information that identifies you personally except as described in this privacy policy.

We may collect or request such personal information in the following ways:

### Correspondence

If you contact us, we may keep a record of the contact information you provide us in order to communicate with you regarding your correspondence.

### Surveys, Promotions or Contests

From time to time, we may conduct surveys, promotions or contests on Do Great Good. Participation in these events is completely voluntary and you will always have a choice whether or not to participate. Any personal information collected as part of the event will only be collected and used for purposes of the event, such as to notify the winners and award prizes for a promotion or contest. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the InfoSpace Sites. 

### User Groups

If you register for a user group on Do Great Good, we request individual user information. If you choose to participate in a user group, your individual user information will be used to qualify you and to contact you for various projects at InfoSpace's discretion. You may opt out of a user group at any time by following the opt out provisions of the user group and your individual user information will be deleted. 

### Tell-A-Friend

If you use our referral services for informing friends or family about any of our services, we may ask you for individual user information and the name and email address of your friend or family member. We will only use the information you provide us to send the person an e-mail inviting them to visit the site or use the service. 

## Third Party Information Gathering

Do Great Good contains links to other websites on the Internet. Please be aware that InfoSpace is not responsible for the information collection and use and privacy practices of such other websites and third parties. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave Do Great Good and to read the privacy statements of each and every other website that may collect their personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by us from the Do Great Good website.

We use third party companies to serve advertisements when you visit Do Great Good. These companies may use information about your visits to Do Great Good in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to Do Great Good, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad-serving company may collect from you. These companies have their own policies as to record keeping and data retention. If you would like more information about this practice, or would like to know your choices about not having this information used by advertising companies, please click here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/.

## Cookies

We and our third party advertising partners (as described above) may place and access cookies on your computer when you use our services. A cookie is a small data file sent to your browser and which may then be stored on your computer. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once you close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following the instructions provided in your Internet browser help file. 

We use cookie technology to track which pages you view and which Web browsers you use on Do Great Good. We may also use cookies to help us provide personalized features and preferences to you in a way that may be linked to individual user information that you elect to share with us. We also use "action tags" to assist in delivering the cookie. These action tags allow us to compile statistics and other data about our customers on an aggregate basis, by embedding a random identifying number on each user's browser. Then we track where that number shows up on our site. 

## Sharing

We may need to disclose the personal information we collect from you when required by law or otherwise necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or violations of our terms of use. 

To the extent we use third party service providers or have co-sponsors of any survey, promotion or contents, the information we collect from you may be accessed or shared as part of the service or event with any such third party or co-sponsor, provided that any such disclosure will be subject to written agreement with such third party or co-sponsor to only use such information for the purpose of the service or event and to not share or make any other use of the information. 

## Mergers; Business Transitions

In the event InfoSpace goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets that involve Do Great Good, the information we collect from Do Great Good will, in most instances, be transferred to the third party as part of the assets. 

## Choice/Opt-out

We desire to keep you in control of the personal information you provide to us. Accordingly, you can request to review, correct, change or remove the personal information we collect and store from you at any time by filling out the [Contact Us](http://search.dogreatgood.com/dgg_sm/ws/contactUs/?_iceurl=true&rfcid=1293&rfcp=content-mid-right) form. 

## Notification of Changes

If we change or update our privacy policy, we will post the new policy in this location and provide an updated effective date for the policy so that you are always aware of our information collection and use practices.

If we change the manner in which we use your personal information from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users by posting a notice on our website for 30 days.

## Special Notification with respect to Children's Privacy (Users under the age of 13)

In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online, Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), which sets forth rules and procedures governing the ways in which websites may collect, use and disclose any personal information for children under the age of 13. In accordance with InfoSpace policy and COPPA regulations, we DO NOT: 

  1. Request or knowingly collect personally identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13 years of age; or 
  2. Knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties; 

It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers 

Questions regarding children's privacy should be directed to: 

InfoSpace, Inc.   
601 108th Avenue NE, Suite 1200   
Bellevue, Washington 98004 USA   
\+ (1) 425.201.6100 phone   
\+ (1) 425.201.6150 fax
